hi guys so today
is Tuesday 23rd of February and after 5
days finally the market has stopped
going down uh so Nifty in performance
nift 50 relatively flat but positive
that is important midcap 50 1.5% up and
strong ending as we can see here small
cap
50 small cap 50 huh 1 % up good and the
bank
Nifty 4% down that's fine so P coming
back to the nifty nift 50 as you
know yesterday
Monday so which is good uh I haven't
received my updated statement from the
mutual fund from UTI but I think my cost
should be around
14,800 so assuming that Nifty or
as of this moment we can see that the
Futures are also positive assuming Nifty
doesn't fall in the next couple of days
so my cost on the Nifty is about 14,800
approximately so that is a tra that is
my next trade so
14,800 and selling at about 15,300
15,400 maybe at 149 or 15 I'll do
another purchase so my that will be
another short trade from 15 to 154 so
this is about the this is about trading
the Nifty a
stock because Market was again positive
and and going up
Etc
LEL anyway Target I have not yet decided
there is lot of positive commentary
regarding the entire metal space so
that's why I bought today Tata steel
hindalco and United phosphorus all three
but targets I'm not yet sure because
although their long-term targets are
very high I'm not looking at those right
now I'm looking at a good 3 to 4% net
margin trade I mean ideally within a
week or maybe even two weeks so that is
uh my target so a man to reiterate Tata
steel Lea hindalco Lea and United
phosphorus Lea on in the metal basket uh
then I also purchased Tata Motors this
was also a good purchase given that it
has gone up 6% today so is p my target
would be about 345 to 350 somewhere
there and I bought one stock of pages an
expensive one but I bought p%
up% up page Industries I'm already
holding one stock of page Industries my
target would be around
31,500 ideally maybe or 32,000 so great
to be back in the positive side of
things Maz let's see how us performs
later today and uh that could play a
role on tomorrow but as of today
tomorrow also seems to be very positive
for the Indian markets so I hope the
momentum continues and let's make some
money I have a good one guys please do
like and subscribe and please do share
your uh your trades as well thank you
bye-bye